Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 4: Clothing, 1878-2010; 52 boxes
  - "27" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black seal, with "27" in orange.
  - "27" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
  - 1948 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    White seal with a tiger, "1948" embroidered in orange and black.
  - "60" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black. "60" in orange.
  - 1967 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and round with orange rim; "1967" in black.
  - Fencing patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    White and rectangular, with two fencing swords crossed in orange, "P," "U," "F," "T" in black.
  - Princeton on the Ohio patch, 1956; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and square, Princeton seal, "Princeton on the Ohio April 5-7-56" in orange/brown and white.
  - Tiger Inn patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black badge with a head of tiger, "Tiger Inn" in green, gray and white.
  - Cleveland Tower patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Princeton seal and motto, with drawing of Cleveland Tower in black.
  - Patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and rectangular, with round corners; "Princeton University" in black.
  - Tiger patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    White and round, with a head of tiger in orange and black.
  - Motto and 8-ball patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Motto above tiger above an 8-ball.
  - University seal patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    University seal.
  - Shield patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Shield on blue background. Square.
    AR.1998.019
  - Patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black circular, "Princeton University" and tiger in orange.
  - 1910 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and black shield with "1910."
    AR.2000.064
  - 1910 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Light orange and black shield with "1910."
  - 1911 bee patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    With bee and 1911.
    AR.1997.042
  - Straw hat, undated; 1 item (Box 53)
    With orange and black band.
  - "1942" hat, undated; 1 item (Box 59)
    Gray hat with "1942" logo.
    AR.2009.089
  - Hat, undated; 1 item (Box 59)
    Off-white hat with orange, black and white band.
  - Lewis Library hat, undated; 1 item (Box 61)
    Orange baseball cap with silver logo. "Peter B. Lewis Library Princeton University."
    AR.2009.004
  - Class of 1938 1st reunion cap, 1939; 1 item (Box 61)
    Orange cap. "38" 1st reunions.
  - Belt, undated; 1 item (Box 62)
    Orange, black and white belt with tiger stripe pattern.
  - Armband?, undated; 1 item (Box 62)
    "P" Orange.
  - Drawstring bag, undated; 1 item (Box 62)
    Black drawstring sack lined with orange.
  - Cloth with "P", undated; 1 item (Box 62)
    17" x 12" with black "P" on orange background.
  - "19 P 13" cummerbund?, undated; 1 item (Box 62)
    Cummerbund? "19 P 13" Orange. 5'
  - Hatband with "22", undated; 1 item (Box 62)
    Orange with black 22.
  - "17" pith helmet, undated; 1 item (Box 65)
    Hard safari hat. White. "17"
  - Anniversary Campaign T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 66)
    Orange with white "ONE" on the front.
  - "P" T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 66)
    Black with orange P on front
  - "Freshman Dink" cap, undated; 1 item (Box 66)
    Freshman Dink
    AR.2003.082
  - "P" T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 66)
    Gray with black P on front
  - Autographed Class of 1958 reunion visor, undated; 1 item (Box 66)
    Class of 1958 reunion visor signed by Jimmy Stewart.
    AR.2003.035
  - Class of 1914 20th reunion pith helmet, 1934; 1 item (Box 67)
    Class of 1914. 20th reunion.
    AR.2000.126
  - Class of 1970 25th Reunion silk scarf, 1995; 1 item (Box 68)
    Class of 1970.
    AR.2001.065
  - 50th reunion sash, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    Orange with black trim and gold writing.
    AR.2001.015
  - Anniversary Campaign T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    Black with Orange "ONE" on front.
  - Class of 1970 cicada bag, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    White and black bag with orange striped handles. Class of 1970 Cicada and Princeton shield pattern.
    AR.2000.130
  - Princeton shield T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    Black with orange triangular Princeton shield on front.
  - "98" hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    With 98 and a tiger head.
  - "98" hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    With 98 and Princeton shields.
  - 1933 football season tie, 1 item (Box 68)
    Orange tie with black "217-8". Commemorates 1933 football season. Princeton scored 217 points.
    AR.2001.056
  - Shield T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    Orange with black triangular Princeton shield on front.
  - Reunions hat band, undated; 1 item (Box 68)
    Orange with black stripes.
    AR.2001.017
  - 1922 hat, undated; 1 item (Box 69)
    Steel gray and orange, "1922" on front.
  - Class of 1928 baseball cap, 1 item (Box 69)
    Class of 1928
    AR.1998.018
  - Scent bag for "'79 Ladies Reception", 1899; 1 item (Box 69)
    "79 Ladies Reception June 10, 99" Orange.
  - Class of 1970 cicada bag, 1990; 1 item (Box 70)
    White and Orange. Class of 1970. 20th reunion. Cicada pattern.
    AR.2002.040
  - Class of 1945 class sweater, undated; 1 item (Box 70)
    Class of 1945
  - Anniversary Campaign hat, undated; 1 item (Box 70)
    Gray with orange and black P on front and "The Anniversary Campaign for Princeton" on back.
  - Class of 1956 T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 71)
    Gray with '56 "In Vino Veritas" on front.
  - Class of 1970 T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 71)
    Orange with 1970 on front.
  - Class of 1970 T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 71)
    White with par '70 and tiger on front.
  - Class of 1970 T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 71)
    Orange with All-Star Team '70 on back an tigers in front.
  - Class of 1957 T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 71)
    Black with '57 on front.
  - Graduate Alumni T-shirt, 1995; 1 item (Box 71)
    Orange. "Graduate Alumni Reunions '95 Princeton" and Picture of a tiger hanging from a double helix.
    AR.2000.044
  - 1926 hat, undated; 1 item (Box 72)
    White with orange band. "1926"
  - Hat with "V" pin, undated; 1 item (Box 72)
    Black with "V" pin attached.
  - "PC 94" hat, circa 1896; 1 item (Box 72)
    Black with orange braid and "PC 94". Pin attached "1746-Sesquicentennial Celebration-1896."
  - Take Back the Night T-shirt, 2003; 1 item (Box 74)
    Take Back the Night Tee Shirt
    AR.2007.019
  - Ivy Award T-shirt, 2003; 1 item (Box 74)
    Ivy Award T-shirt. "2003 Winner of Restaurants and Institutions' Ivy Award."
    AR.2004.007
  - Class of 1935 T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 74)
    Class of 1935 T-shirt. White shirt with orange flags "35."
    AR.2005.024
  - Class of 1970 25th reunion beer jacket, 1995; 1 item (Box 74)
    1970's 25th. Cicada pattern.
  - Class of 1942 Tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Class of 1942. Black tie with orange logo.
  - Tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Orange.
  - "21" tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Orange. "21"
  - "1926" tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Orange. "1926"
  - "1932" tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Black. "1932"
  - Striped tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Black and orange. Diagonal stripes.
  - Striped tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Black and orange. Vertical thin stripes.
  - Tie with U. seals, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Black with U. seals.
  - Tigers tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Black with tigers.
  - 27s tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Orange with black 27's.
  - "31" tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Black with repeated people, one with "'31" on orange shirt.
    AR.1998.045
  - "28" tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Black with orange cannons(?) with "28" on them.
  - 1935 football season tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Orange with "753-78" in black. Commemorates 1935 football team's winning season (753 total points vs. opponents' 78).
  - Striped tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Orange, black and white diagonal stripes.
  - Hat, undated; 1 item (Box 81)
    White with orange and black band.
  - Class of 1970 cicada baseball hat, undated; 1 item (Box 81)
    Class of 1970 cicada pattern on front and leaping tiger on back
    AR.2002.043
  - Class of '98 tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Class of '98 tie. Orange and black diagonal stripes.
    AR.2003.061
  - Class of 1935 tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Class of 1935 tie. Black tie with orange flags.
  - Class of 1932 tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Class of 1932 tie. Black tie with orange lettering.
  - Class of 1916 tie, 1961; 1 item (Box 83)
    Class of 1916. 45th reunion tie. Black tie with orange stripes and orange lettering.
    AR.2007.026
  - Tiger tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Black tie with orange tiger cartoons.
    AR.2005.048
  - Striped tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Striped tie and orange and black.
  - Class of 1916 tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Class of 1916 tie. Orange and black stripes.
  - Belt with tiger head buckle, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Black leather with tiger head buckle.
  - Belt with snake buckle, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Orange and black ribbon with snake buckle.
  - Bow tie with 1927, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Black with orange 1927.
  - "22" black necktie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    "22 " Black.
  - "22" orange necktie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    "22" Orange plaid.
  - Knit tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Black and orange. Horizontal thick stripes. Knit.
  - "98" knit tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Orange. "98" Knit.
  - "39" tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Black with orange "39."
  - Yale/Princeton tie, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    Light blue. Repeated design of bottles with "VAT 39" on them and half Yale bulldog and half tiger behind them.
  - 1890 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    90. Black with two stripes.
  - 1890 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    90. Black with orange stripes.
  - 1891 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    91. Black with orange stripes.
  - 1892 hatband, undated; 2 items (Box 83)
    92. Tigers on black.
  - 1892 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    92. Orange.
  - 1894 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    94. Black.
  - 1895 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    95. Black.
  - 1895 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 83)
    95. Orange.
  - Beer Jacket, undated; 1 item (Box 88)
    1929
  - Colonial Club t-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 88)
    Blue. Colonial Club.
  - Graduate Alumni '96 T-shirt, 1996; 1 item (Box 88)
    Orange. "Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Reunions '96". Picture of "The Study of Tiger" Da Vinci.
  - Graduate Alumni '97 T-shirt, 1997; 1 item (Box 88)
    White. "Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Reunions 1997" and picture of "The Study of Tiger" on front.
  - Graduate Alumni '99 T-shirt, 1999; 1 item (Box 88)
    White. APGA and tiger on front. '99 and tiger and "Princeton Graduate Alumni" on back.
  - Class of 1970 tT-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 90)
    Orange with '70 and a sailboat on front.
  - Class of 1970 cicada T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 90)
    White. 1970 inside cicada with Princeton Shield design. Different Collars.
  - Class of 1970 cicada T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 90)
  - Class of 1970 cicada T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 90)
  - Graduate School Centennial T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 90)
    White. "The Centennial of the Graduate of the Graduate School."
  - Graduate College T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box S-000001)
    White. Graduate College Shield. Grad-a-pult on back.
  - Graduate reunions '98 T-shirt, 1998; 1 item (Box S-000001)
    White. "APGA reunions '98 Tiger". Picture of "The Study of Tiger" Da Vinci.
  - Graduate Alumni T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box S-000001)
    Black. "APGA" on front. Tiger and "Graduate Alumni" on back.
  - Graduate Alumni T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box S-000001)
    Orange. "Princeton Graduate Alumni" and Tiger holding Grad. College on front.
  - Cleveland Tower T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box S-000001)
    White. "Lived Through it. The Renovation of Cleveland Tower. The Graduate College" and before and after pictures of the tower on front.
  - Socks, undated; 1 item (Box 94)
    Orange
  - Tie with "30", undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    Class of 1930? Black tie with orange lettering "30" and tiger face.
  - Tie with "30", undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    Class of 1930? Black tie with orange lettering "30" and tiger roaring.
  - Triangle Club tie, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    Princeton Triangle Club. Red tie with gold logo "PTC" with triangle.
  - 1895 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    "1895". Orange.
  - 1897 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    "1897" with seal. White.
  - 1899 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    99. Orange.
  - 1901 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1901. Orange.
  - 1901 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1901. Orange with black border.
  - 1901 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1901. Black.
  - 1901 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    01. Black.
  - 1903 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    03. Black with tigers.
  - 1903 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    03. White with seal.
  - Armband with 22, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    Orange 22.
  - 1910 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1910. Black with orange stripes.
  - 1910 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1910. Orange.
  - 1912 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
  - 1913 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1913. Orange.
  - 1915 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
  - 1918 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
  - 1921 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1921. Orange.
  - 1921 hatband with stripe, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
    1921. Orange with black stripe.
    George Packer Berry '21
  - 1930 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
  - 1932 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
  - 1939 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000002)
  - Class of 1970 20th reunion pith helmet, 1990; 1 item (Box S-000003)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. With reunion pin.
  - Women's Center T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box S-000004)
    Women's Center T-shirt. "This is what a feminist looks like."
    AR.2009.101
  - Chemistry department T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box S-000004)
    White Chemistry Department T-shirt. Orange and black shield with "Princeton Chemistry."
    AR.2009.100
  - Graduate Alumni 2009 T-shirt, 1 item (Box S-000004)
    Black T-shirt. Association of Princeton Graduate Alumni Reunions 2009. "Galileo's Galactic Magic."
    AR.2009.050
  - Class of 1985 25th reunion shorts, 2010; 1 item (Box S-000004)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Black shorts.
  - Class of 1985 25th reunion "Crew" T-shirt, 2010; 1 item (Box S-000004)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Neon green T-shirt and black lettering "Crew."
  - Class of 1985 Reunions Run T-shirt, 2010; 1 item (Box S-000004)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. White t-shirt with "PURR" logo. Princeton University Reunions Run.
  - Class of 1985 25th reunion T-shirt, 2010; 1 item (Box S-000004)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Orange T-shirt with black reunions logo.
  - Class of 1985 20th reunion T-shirt, 2005; 1 item (Box S-000004)
    Class of 1985. 20th reunion. White T-shirt with black lettering "We Won the Clancy!"
  - 1904 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    04. Orange.
  - 1904 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1904 Orange.
  - 1904 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1904 Black.
  - 1905 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1905 Orange.
  - 1907 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1907 Orange. Pointed lettering.
  - 1907 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1907. Orange.
  - 1907 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1907 L. Red and blue.
  - 1907 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1907. Black and orange striped.
  - 1907 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1907. Black with two stripes.
  - 1907 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    "07 L. Blue with red stripe.
  - 1907 camels hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1907. Tent with camels.
  - 1908 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1908. Orange. Pointed lettering.
  - 1908 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1908. Green.
  - Eating club hatbands, undated; 9 items (Box S-000005)
    Eating club bands with club colors such as Ivy's green and gold
  - Class of 1913 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    Black with 1913 stitched in orange.
  - Class of 1942 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000005)
    1942. Orange and black felt.
    AR.2000.077
  - Hatband with '74, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    74 and U seal. White.
  - Hatband with '76, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    76. Orange.
  - Hatband with '78, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    78. Orange with black stripes.
  - Hatband with '78, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    78. Black with orange stripes.
  - Hatband with '79, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    79. Blue numbers. White.
  - Hatband with '81, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    81. Black and orange striped.
  - Hatband with '86, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    86. Black and orange striped.
  - Hatband with '86, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    86. Black with three stripes.
  - Hatband with '86, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    86. Orange with black stripe.
  - Hatband with '86, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    86 with U seal. White.
  - Hatband with 87s, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    87's. Black.
  - Hatband with '87, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    87. Black and orange striped.
  - Hatband with '89, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    89. Orange.
  - Hatband with '89, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    89. Black with three stripes.
  - Hatband with '76, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    76. Orange satin.
  - Reunion hatband with 73, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    White, Princeton seal and motto in orange, black and gold, "'73" in black.
  - Reunion hatband with 79, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    Orange with black rims, "'79" in black.
  - Hatband with '03, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    03. Black with stripe.
  - 1908 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    1908. Orange with stripes.
  - 1908 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    08. White with orange and black stripes.
  - 1909 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    09. Orange with tiger.
  - 1909 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    1909. Black and orange.
  - 1910 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box S-000006)
    1910. Black with orange stripe.
  - 1909 hatband, 1 item (Box S-000006)
    White, 1909.
    AR.1996.041
  - Tie, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Black tie with orange stripes.
    AR.2009.137
  - Class of 1926 tie, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Class of 1926. Orange tie with "Princeton 1926" in black and tiger logo.
  - Tie, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
  - Tie with tigers, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Black tie with tiger pattern.
  - Tie, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Black tie with orange double stripe pattern.
  - Nassoons tie, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Nassoons tie. Black tie with orange stripes and Nassoons logo.
    AR.2011.041
  - Hatband with '87, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    87. Black with thin orange stripe.
  - Hatband with '88, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    88. Single eights.
  - Hatband with '88, undated; 2 items (Box S-000007)
    88. Two hatbands with entwining eights.
  - Class of 1970 cicada bandana, 1990; 1 item (Box 121)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. In locusts parentis. Cicada pattern.
  - Reunion fabric samples, undated; 1 item (Box S-000008)
    Binder of "Princeton University Reunion Fabrics." Individually labeled fabric patches. Includes "Collected Samples of Reunion Jackets, Neckties, Patches, Etcetera"
    AR.2003.091; assembled by Van Zandt Williams, Jr. '65 and the Alumni Council Committee on Princetoniana
  - Black purse with orange lining, undated; 1 item (Box 125)
    Orange lined purse.
  - Black purse with orange lining, bow and "Jennis 7-2-85", 1885; 1 item (Box 125)
    Orange lined purse. With bow and embroidery. "Jennis 7-2-85"
  - Princeton '98 Class Day" Pouch, 1898; 1 item (Box 125)
    "Princeton '98 Class Day" White leather. Tobacco?
  - Pocket from 1905 Class Jacket, undated; 1 item (Box 142)
    White and square, "PU" in black, "1905" in gold.
    AR.1995.061
  - Small cloth with '78, circa 1878; 1 item (Box 142)
    Black '78 on orange background.
  - Linen coaster with "79", undated; 1 item (Box 171)
    Linen, white and round; two tigers along the circumference in pink, gold, white and black; "79" in between in pink.
  - Tiger head patch, undated; 1 item (Box 171)
    Tiger head in orange/yellow, black, white and red.
  - Quilted square with '79, undated; 1 item (Box 171)
    11" x 11" with tigers and '79.
  - Handkerchief from Rutgers football game, 1947; 1 item (Box 172)
    Orange paint on it from raid at Rutgers before 1947 or 1948 football game.
    AR.1996.110
  - Cloth with '39, 1939; 1 item (Box 182)
    39 emblems stitched into piece of cloth.
  - Handkerchief with 78, undated; 1 item (Box 182)
    Orange and white. "78"
    Given by Mrs. Graham Hunter, daughter of John Henry Kerr, class of 1878. Used
  - Rutgers football centennial T-shirt, 1969; 1 item (Box 185)
    Football Centennial with Rutgers "Beat Princeton" - Rutgers T-shirt.
    at class reunions.
  - Handkerchief, undated; 1 item (Box 186)
    Black and orange. Silk.
  - Fiftieth reunion sash, undated; 1 item (Box 186)
    Orange with black braid on edges. "Fiftieth Reunion."
  - "P" sweater, undated; 1 item (Box 186)
    Black sweater turtleneck with striped sleeves. Orange "P" on front.
  - Striped cloth, undated; 1 item (Box 190)
    Black and orange stripes.
  - "19 Tenth 46", 1956; 1 item (Box 190)
    Black and orange stripes. Tag on inside "19 Tenth 46"
    AR.1996.055; John MacFadyen
  - "Vat 49" T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 190)
    Orange. Black bottle in picture, "Vat 49"
  - "46" T-shirt, undated; 1 item (Box 190)
    White with "46" on front.
  - Doctoral hood, undated; 1 item (Box S-000009)
    Black and orange.
  - Doctoral hood, undated; 1 item (Box S-000009)
  - Orange Jacket with "16", undated; 1 item (Box S-000010)
    "16" on pocket.
  - Class of 1920 Jacket, undated; 1 item (Box 196)
    Black and orange, "20"
  - Battle of Princeton 22 jacket, undated; 1 item (Box 196)
    Jacket patterned. Battle of Princeton 22.
  - White linen knickers, undated; 1 item (Box 199)
    Part of reunion costume.
  - Class Jacket with "49er", undated; 1 item (Box 199)
    White denim, "49er" on back.
  - 1946 Jacket and pants set, undated; 1 item (Box 201)
    "1946" on jacket. Orange and white striped corduroy.
  - White Beer jacket, undated; 1 item (Box 201)
    "NBA We did our part."
    Given by Frank Buchner '34.
  - Kilt, sporeen, cap, white cloth boot tops with buttons, undated; 1 item (Box 202)
    Orange and black buffalo plaid.
  - Coveralls, undated; 1 item (Box 221)
    Off-white front. Black and orange sleeves and back.
  - Socks, undated; 1 item (Box 221)
  - Class of 1942 tie, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Class of 1942. Orange tie with white tiger
  - Black and Orange umbrella hat, undated; 1 item (Box 115)
  - William of Orange-Nassau shoulder patch from Korean War, circa 1951; 1 item (Box 116)
    Coat of arms of William of Orange-Nassau; from sleeve of Dutch troops in Korean War.
    EX4910; Dr. Fred B. Rogers (1947), Friend Temple University Hospital
  - Class of 1969 wristband, 2009; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1969. 40th reunion. Wristband.
    AR.2009.094
- Series 5: Dishware, 1801-2010; 102 boxes; 12 items
  Dishware includes traditional ceramic plates, bowls, and mugs, as well as glassware. The series also contains more ephemeral containers for food and drinks, such as beer cans, plastic cups, bottles, and snack bags.
  - Class of 1978 popcorn bags, undated; 3 items (Box 96)